# **OKOSUN MARY EGHONGHON**

08028430564 | okosunmaryeghonghon@gmail.com

#### **OBJECTIVE**

A result-oreinted front-end developer dedicated to creating and user-friendly websites. I am also interested in leveraging analytical skills and strong attention to details in order to deliver original and efficient web solutions. I am keen to gain more experience in a company willing to offer me a placement among their developers and I would offer my full commitment and be a pleasant and friendly addition to your team.

## **SKILLS**

- · Proficiency in HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Working knowledge of React, a JavaScript framework.
- · Working knowledge of PHP for server-side scripting.
- Working knowledge of Database Management using MySQL
- · Very familiar to agile practices of Software Development.
- Good communication skills and interpersonal relationship skills.
- · Strong problem-solving and analytical skills.
- · Experience on Microsoft Office products (word, powerpoint).

# **EDUCATION**

University of Benin, Benin City, Edo State.

2017
BSc. Biochemistry
Second Class Upper Division

Femson Immaculate College, Ibafo, Ogun State

2013

West African Examination Council WASSCE

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# DUFUNA

2020 - 2021

Full Stack Developer Intern - Remote

- Worked with programming languages like JavaScript, CSS, PHP and MySQL.
- o Built various projects such as a TODO app using React.
- The use of version control system; Git and GitHub.
- Developed Optimised Codes.
- · Participated in team hackathons.

#### CURATOR UNIVERSITY

2018 - 2019

Data Scientist - Akure, Ondo State.

- Use of scikit-learn and Matlab for data visualisation.
- o Handled tutorials for data Science using Python.
- o Basic knowledge of machine learning algorithms such as linear regression.
- Participated in various team hackathons.

## NIGERIAN WOMEN TECHSTERS -Tech4Dev

2018 - 2018

Web Developer Intern - Benin city, Edo State.

o HTML, CSS and jQuery.

# **VOLUNTEER**

• AWNET Enterprises- Edo State.

Use of WordPress to update a church's website on a weekly basis.

In charge of the website maintenance.

# AFRICA CODE WEEK- Edo State.

Partnered with the Edo State Government in tutoring secondary school students across Edo State on Scratch as a programming language.

Assisted in the training of teachers on use of scratch in their respective schools across the state.

# **ACHIEVEMENTS & AWARDS**

• Got the 1st runner up position in the Breast Cancer Prevention 2018 Digital Hackathon held in Ondo State organized by BRECAN sponsored by Access Bank.

## **INTERESTS**

- Writing
- Reading
- Sport Volleyball

## **REFERENCE**

• Available on Request - ""